(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Raj:)I always thought if I had a white name,
it would be Gavin.
- Keep reading. What does it say?
- No, I don't know if I should.
(Raj:)If she wanted me to know about her blog,
she would've told me.
(Raj:)- It's almost like I'm reading her diary.
- It's exactly what it's like. Keep reading.
(Raj:)No, this is creepy.
(Howard:)Oh... I think we were looking at creepy in the
rearview mirror when I put up that camera.
(Raj:)It's not creepy. Don't listen to him.
Ooh, who's got the sweetest kisses?
(Howard:)Should I go?
(Leonard:)With all the TV Sheldon was talking about,
I had the greatest idea ever.
It blows away my idea for a Star Wars-themed
coffee shop called Brewbacca's.